50cubes.com 2013-07-10

# 

**50 CUBES INC.**

**PRIVACY POLICY**

50 Cubes Inc. is committed to maximizing your experience on our website within a trusted environment. This privacy policy explains how we collect, protect, use and share information gathered about you online. We hope this disclosure will help increase your confidence in the 50 Cubes website ([ _www.50cubes.com_](http://www.50cubes.com/) ) and enhance your experience. Please note that this privacy policy applies only to information submitted and collected online at our website or in any of our games, including _Mall World_ , _Fashion Designer_ , _Fashion Tale_ and _Shop Spot_. It does not apply to information that you may submit to us offline, or to websites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we may link.

**_(1) What types of information does 50 Cubes collect and how will it be used?_**    

50 Cubes only collects information from you on a voluntary basis. We do not send spam or sell email addresses. So that we can provide you with the most efficient and enhanced experience, we request that you register for a personal account accessible through a confidential password and screen name that you select. For purposes of registration, we collect identifiable information about you such as your name, email address, and demographic information such as age, gender and zip code. We also may collect your IP address, browser type, domain name, access times and referring website address. This information is collecting during registration or in response to specific requests from you, for things such as signing up for an email newsletter, chat room, or other online information service we may offer, entering a contest, answering a survey, or contacting us. Surveys are conducted strictly for internal profiling purposes and only keep track of anonymous demographic data (e.g., your age, usage of the 50 Cubes website, favorite games). Our website contains links through which an online user can email us. We collect personal information contained in the email for the purpose of responding to a user's questions and/or comments. From time to time, we may post on our website job openings at 50 Cubes and provide an email address to which interested applicants can submit their resume. Although we can assure you that any personal information contained in a resume will be used solely for its intended purpose (i.e., to evaluate the applicant's qualifications), such information is not subject to this privacy policy.   

No matter what method we use to collect information and no matter how we use that information, we will only collect the information deemed reasonably necessary to fulfill your online requests and our legitimate business objectives.    

From time to time we may offer marketing or promotional programs in which eligible and selected users may receive an award, compensation or other benefit based on participation. The conditions of any such program are stated in our Terms of Use Agreement accessible on this screen. You agree that we may use your information to inform you about any such program we may offer and to communicate with you if you elect to participate in such a program. **_(2) 50 Cubes does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13_**

This is not a website directed to children under the age of 13, and 50 Cubes does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 years of age. If you are under 13 years of age you should not use this website, and under no circumstances should you send information about yourself to 50 Cubes. If 50 Cubes discovers that a child under the age of 13 has provided 50 Cubes with personally identifiable information, 50 Cubes will immediately delete that child's personally identifiable information from the website and preclude the child from further access. 

**_(3) What happens if I refuse to provide my personal information to 50 Cubes?_**    

If you choose not to submit personally identifiable information when requested, you may not be able to access certain areas of our website and you may considerably limit the services we can provide you. To simply access our website, however, you do not need to give us any personally identifiable information.

**_(4) Does 50 Cubes use cookies or other means to collect information?_**    

You will know when personally identifiable information is collected because you will be asked to fill out a form. However, we may collect some information about you by using data collection technology, so that it may not be readily apparent to you that it is being collected. For instance, when you come to our website, your IP address is collected so that we know where to send information you are requesting. An IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet. A "cookie" is a small file or record-keeping device that websites often store on a user's computer. (You can disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer.) We do not use IP addresses or cookies to collect personally identifiable information, such as your name, or to link this information to personally identifiable information already collected about you. This information may be used to make our website more interesting and useful to you. Additionally, we may combine this information with personally identifiable information to identify a user in order to enforce compliance with our Terms of Use Agreement, or to protect our service, website or users to the website.

**_(5) With whom does 50 Cubes share my personally identifiable information?_**    

From time to time, we may employ and share your personal information with vendors who use it solely to provide support for the internal operations of our website (e.g., technical support and network delivery). These entities will not use your personally identifiable information for any other purpose, and have agreed to maintain the confidentiality, security, and integrity of the personal information they obtain from us.

It is our policy not to share, sell or rent your personal information to any company not directly related to 50 Cubes as a provider or customer. 50 Cubes reserves the right to share your personally identifiable information with our parent or affiliated companies. Further, 50 Cubes may sell, transfer or otherwise disclose user information, including personally identifiable information, in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, the sale of substantially all assets, or other fundamental corporate change.

We may disclose your personal information in the good faith belief that we are required to do so by law or to comply with legal processes, respond to any claims or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of 50 Cubes staff or the public.

**_(6) Third party advertisements and content_**    

When you are using the 50 Cubes website, certain content, including advertisements, may be created or hosted by a third party. Such third parties may place cookies and/or use web beacons, which may be used to identify some of your preferences or to recognize you if you have previously had contact with them. We do not control the use of such technology by third parties, the information they collect, or how they use such information. 50 Cubes does not disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties serving ads or other content on our website.

**_(7) What is 50 Cubes' policy regarding links to third party websites?_**    

You should be aware that while you are on a website operated by us, you may be directed to links to other websites. The privacy policies of these other websites are beyond our control and we take no responsibility for their practices. Because we cannot guarantee that the privacy policies of these websites meet our high standards, we recommend that you read the privacy policy of the website to which you link before you submit any personal information.

**_(8) How can I access my personal information?_**    

If you wish to review, update, or delete any personal information that we may have collected about you, please contact us via email at [_privacy@50cubes.com_](mailto:privacy@50cubes.com).

**_(9) What safeguards does 50 Cubes use to protect my personally identifiable information?_**    

We maintain appropriate safeguards that ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the personally identifiable information we collect from all users. The 50 Cubes account of every user is password protected. Personal information collected by us is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public and are only accessible by authorized employees. We also have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

**_(10) What are my privacy rights if I am located outside the United States of America?_**    

50 Cubes makes an effort to protect the personally identifiable information of all users of its website. We attempt to comply with local data protection and consumer rights laws to the extent they may apply to 50 Cubes' services. If you are uncertain whether this privacy policy conflicts with the applicable local privacy laws where you are located, you should not submit your personally identifiable information to 50 Cubes. If you are located within the European Union, you should be aware that your personally identifiable information will be transferred to the United States of America, the laws of which may be deemed by the European Union to have inadequate data protection. If you are located in a country outside the United States of America and voluntarily submit personally identifiable information to us, you thereby consent to the general use of such information as provided in this privacy policy and to the transfer of that information to, and/or storage of that information in, the United States of America.

**_(11) How do I ask a question or file a complaint?_**    

If you have any questions, complaints or comments regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us via email at [privacy@50cubes.com](mailto:privacy@50cubes.com). If you have general questions not related to privacy, you can visit our customer support page. 

**_(12) Changes in the 50 Cubes privacy policy_**    

We reserve the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time. If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our website so that you and other users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. You should also check back from time to time to ensure you are aware of any changes. If we are going to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify you and others via email or by placing a prominent notice on our website. 

**By using this website, you signify your assent to the 50 Cubes Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this privacy policy, please do not use this website. Your continued use of this website will signify your acceptance of these changes.**

This 50 Cubes Privacy Policy was updated August 10, 2011.
